On Wednesday, Israel bombed Al-Ahli Hospital, or the Baptist Hospital in Gaza.
And this was a massacre.
More than 500 people were killed instantly.
And there were so many injured.
This is really dangerous because Israel claimed that it did not.
And it was an Islamic Jihad rocket.
And they denied it.
And they lied.
But many investigative journalists confirmed that it was a lie.
And confirmed that it was indeed an Israeli airstrike.
And that the rocket that they used is actually an American rocket.
So, why I'm talking about this now?
Because they've just warned the Red Crescent and Al-Quds Hospital, Jerusalem Hospital in Gaza,
to evacuate because they're going to bomb it.
And how are you going to evacuate 400 patients where we don't have the resources, the ambulances,
most of them are targeted.
Not only that, but most of them are in critical conditions.
More than 12,000 displaced people are taking shelter in that hospital.
This is going to be another massacre if the world does not act right now and demand that this has to stop.
Guys, I'm urging the international community.
I'm urging everyone who has power, any kind of power, to stop this immediately.
People, there's no safe place to go to in Gaza.
This is going to be another massacre.
Most of the people I know are now taking refuge in Al-Quds Hospital.
My neighbors, my friends, my family members.
So, I don't know.
I don't know how this is still happening.
And you need to act right now.